本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 小癫羊 Floralin 许块块 涕涕真是naive
校对： 许块块   后期： 唱唱反调
哦 天啊
Oh, boo ya.
现在让我瞧瞧有什么可大惊小怪的
Now let's see what all the fuss is about.
这个太像突击者了
Oh, this is so Raiders.
希望这个方舟里能有更少的纳粹面孔
Here's hoping this Ark contains less Nazi-face-melting goodness.
哦 是尤那达人
Oh, the Una Mens...
确实是 他们来了
Indeed. They are coming.
而且他们很饿
And they will be hungry.
让我走 僵尸男!
Let me go, zombie boy!
惠彻 等等
Whicher, hold on...
她已被捕 竟敢玷污血法
She is claimed. Yet dares to defile the blood laws.
她将被交给尤那达人
She will be delivered by the Una Mens.
而你伙计 你应该被交给一个牙医
And you need to be delivered to a dentist, buddy.
你的呼吸问起来像是雪人的屁眼
Your breath smells like the anus of a Yeti.
来自袭击避难所的人类大胆言论啊
Bold talk from the human who attacked a place of sanctuary.
惠彻 你犯了一个错误
Whicher, you're making a mistake.
你应该放她走
You should just let her go.
我一直告诉你我不是人类
I keep telling you I am not human.
蛮可爱的嘛
That's cute.
你看到了 这个女人不是你要找的
As you can see, this one cannot be the one you're looking for.
- 她是... - 宝贝 纯异种啊
- She is... - All Fae, baby.
感受下热度吧!
Feel the heat!
这怎么可能
How is it possible?
- 我弄错了? - 嘿 妖无完妖
- I am mistaken? - Hey, "pobody's nerfect".
我们会带她离开这的 使者先生
We'll get her out of here, your emissary.
下次我见到她 她的皮会被剥掉
The next time I see this one, her skin will line
放在在尤那达人的神圣屋中
the Una Mens Holy chambers.
- 我把他骗的团团转 - 走吧
- I totally had him. - Let's go.
谢谢 无为侦探
Thanks, Detective Do-Nothings.
你怎么不用厚重的狼爪一下拍在他屁股上?
What, you couldn't have whomped his ass with your massive wolf paws?
然后错过了秀? 不错啊 小火花飞溅
What, and miss the show? Nice work, Sparky.
太悬了 肯吉
That was too close, Kenz.
那些临时能量不是个好主意
These temporary powers are not a good idea.
不过很有必要
Yeah, but necessary,
因为我是个恐怖分子 记得吗?
because I'm a terrorist, remember?
闻起来像向日葵和夏敦埃酒的恐怖分子?
You terrorists all smell like sunflowers and Chardonnay?
好吧 我得带汀科贝尔回家了 好吗
Okay, I'm gonna take Timkerbell home, all right?
是啊
Yep.
- 你先请 - 我做文书工作吧
- After you. - I'll go do the paperwork.
向日葵?? 什么烂比喻
Sunflowers?? Nice.
这儿没人 戴森 别闻了
No one's here, Dyson. Stop sniffing.
只有你 我 还有丁字裤 哈?
Just you, me and the, uh, thongs, huh?
顺便说一句 这儿的丁字裤真不少
That's a whole lot of thongs, by the way.
你要知道 这些都是业务需要
Well, I will have you know, that these are all business thongs.
我根本不想知道那是什么意思
I don't even wanna know what that means.
不过我明白你为什么需要这么多丁字裤
I can see why you need all this stuff, though.
一种填补空虚的方式嘛
Sort of fills the place up a bit.
好吧 如果你想问的话 我不孤单 老狼
Well, I am not lonely, if that is what you're asking, wolfie.
事实上 我没问
I wasn't, actually.
和我在这里你怎么会孤单?
Why would you be lonely with me here?
那是个...不错的问题
That is a very... good question...
该死...
Shit...
是不是所有的狼都这么浪漫?
Are all wolves this romantic?
我只是在想黑尔 我...
I'm just thinking about Hale, I...
你想的挺开
That's very open-minded of you.
他疯狂地爱着你 对吗?
He's crazy about you, right?
我们什么时候开始...这样的?
Since when are we... this?
议会的来了
More Council douche-hats.
不是 闻起来太过...愉快了
No, smells a little too, uh... pleasant.
你好
Hello.
请你...
Please...
我需要和天才私家侦探聊聊
I need to speak with the talented private investigator.
我叫艾尔弗
My name is Aife.
女士 我记得你
I remember you, lady.
你让阿什说话像个蝙蝠侠 滚吧
You made Ash who talks like Batman, go boom.
哦 这个季节穿山羊皮? 你这个红颜祸水
Oh, suede, in this weather? You beautiful badass.
- 让她走 - 我不是来这打架的
- Let her go. - Look, I'm not here to fight.
我需要帮助 帮我找到女儿
I need help, finding my daughter.
她的名字叫波
Her name is Bo.
波
Bo.
听起来像个哥们名字 我说的对吗?
Kind of a dude's name, am I right?
当你不知你是谁时 生活会很艰辛
Life is hard when you don't know who you are.
当你知道真相后 生活会更艰难
It's harder when you don't know what you are.
我的爱伴随死神的降临
My love carries a death sentence.
我迷失了多年
I was lost for years.
在藏匿中找寻
Searching while hiding.
那个不为人知的属于我的世界
Only to find that I belonged to a world hidden from humans.
但我已厌倦躲藏 我要过自己想要的生活
I won't hide anymore. I will live the life I choose.
第四季第一集 为了记忆
4x01 - In Memoriam
所以你是淫妖?
So you are a Succubus?
那位曾试图刺杀光明派异种长老的淫妖
The Succubus who tried to assassinate the Light Fae elders.
- 我心里七上八下的 - 现在呢?
- I was agitated. - And now?
比以前好点 现在我有个更高的目标了
I'm less agitated. And I have a higher purpose:
就是找到我丢失的女儿
to find the daughter that I lost.
哦...我们之前见过
Oh... we've met before.
你没给我留下什么印象
You didn't leave much of an impression.
亲爱的 我之前见过很多男人
Ha. Darling, I've 'met' many men before.
无论如何 他们之后都会对女朋友说
And whatever they claim later in front of their lady friends,
他们印象深刻
they're always impressed.
但是我说的是近期 在塔夫特的...实验室
But I was speaking more recently. At Taft's... lab.
确实是 你当时在那儿
That's right, you were there.
所以你有一个三十岁的女儿?
So, you have a thirty year old daughter?
一位从未被听说或看见过的成年女儿?
A grown daughter no one has ever heard of, or seen... ?
是真的 没有任何记录
It's true, there's no record,
或者生理标志能表明我曾经生育
or physical indications that I ever gave birth.
然而淫妖的武器就是她身体
Though a Succubus' weapon is her body,
所以可以说 武器不会磨损
so there would be no wear and tear, so to speak.
你想自己找找吗?
Would you like to see for yourself?
找妊娠纹? 算了吧
Scanning for stretch marks? Pass.
我打心底知道我生了个女儿
I know in my heart I gave birth to a baby girl.
我知道会给她取我母亲的名字
I know I would have named her after my own mother.
我还知道这是她
And I know this is her.
当我发现照片的时候我就知道
I knew as soon as I found the photo.
我赌五块那是她家猫的照片
Five bucks says it's a picture of her cat.
我没疯
I'm not crazy.
这个女人真... 漂亮
This woman is... beautiful.
如果你迷恋脸蛋和身材的话 随便了
Yeah, if you're into, like, faces and bodies. Whatever...
我们不感兴趣
We're not interested.
- 抱歉... - 我知道 你持怀疑态度
- Sorry... - You're skeptical, I get it.
我爸爸没养过傻子
My Daddy didn't raise no fool.
那是记忆线圈
That's a Recuerdo coil.
铁证如山 异种的记忆被弄乱了
That's hard proof that a Fae has been messing with her memory.
我只想知道为什么
I just want to know why.
我会付钱 当然了 我会给一大笔
I'll pay, of course. I'll pay well.
您的女儿 立马找到
One daughter, coming right up.
当然 是收取费用的情况下
With, you know, expenses, naturally.
那是自然
Naturally.
- 抱歉 - 等等 现在?
- Excuse me. - Wait, now?
每天的同一时间
Same time. Every day.
你已经找了一个月了 一无所获
You've been going for a month and you have found squat.
她救了我
She rescued me.
戴森 她开车带你跌下悬崖
Dyson, she drove you off a cliff.
我要是不转形的话早死了
And I would have died if I hadn't shifted.
所以我要找到塔米辛 找出原因...
That's why I need to find Tamsin. Find out why...
好吧 你欠我一次 让我独自面对客户和账单
Okay, you owe me for leaving me alone with the client, and the tab.
好消息 她打算接你的案子
Good news. She's gonna take your case.
你很幸运 肯吉是最棒的
And you're lucky. 'Cause Kenzi is the best.
我也赶时间 这周是军舰周
I'd like to get going, as well. It's Fleet Week.
- 好的 - 还需要点别的吗
- Okay. - Can I get you anything else?
- 让我来 - 棒极了
- Allow me. - Great.
我现在有些缺钱
I'm a little short right now.
也许我可以下次再来
Maybe I could come back sometime,
给你补偿...
make it up to you...
天啊 好的
God... yes.
女士 你缺经纪人嘛
Lady, what you need is some kind of manager.
新嗜好吗
New hobby?
你跟史黛拉闹矛盾了
Is this because of what happened between you and Stella?
什么
What??
没 没闹矛盾
No. Nothing happened.
没闹 是闹分手 还是你让她怀孕了
Nothing like it's just a break or nothing like you knocked her up.
别碰...
Don't touch... !
有些突发事件
Something's out of step.
有人干扰了时空平衡
Someone's been messing with the balance of space and time.
我打赌是新议会 他们看似很蛋疼
My money's on the new Council. They seem really easily butt hurt.
尤那达人是接近全知的委员会
The Una Mens are a near-omniscent council
异种当权唯一的目的...
of Fae authority who's sole purpose...
...确保旧规章能继续
...is to ensure the old laws are followed. Uh huh.
这是什么种子
What's with the seed?
尤那达人的一个象征
It's a symbol of the Una Mens.
他们袭击我们的移民队
They're descending on our little 'colony' because
因为之前几年里 事情真的变得很糟糕
things have gotten real messy in the past few years.
都怪比伯太红
I blame Bieber Fever.
他们 呃 不会...
They, um, wouldn't do...
使记忆丧失 是吗
memory loss, would they?
不会 尤那达人从不会做这种
No, the Una Mens would never stoop
有失身份的...狡猾之举
to something so... subtle.
等等...怎么了
Wait... why?
呃 新客户
Oh, uh, new client.
我得打击当地一个使人失忆的异种
I need a beat on the local Fae that can cause amnesia.
- 失忆症 - 嗯
- Amnesia? - Mm-hmm.
尖吻鲈 医生
Dr. Snook.
他是奥坎克斯 鱼类异种 靠记忆为食
He's an ortenax; fish Fae; feeds off memories.
同时也是一位眼科医生
Moonlights as an eye Doc.
鲑鱼类 明白了
Trout-tometrist. Got it!
说到医生 劳伦怎么样了
Speaking of Doctors, any word on Lauren?
她在塔夫特的手术中施计 之后又违背阿什
She tricked Taft during surgery, after disobeying the Ash.
她抛弃了光明派异种
She abandoned the light Fae.
她救了戴森的命
She saved Dyson's life!
很难搞懂路易斯医生是敌是友
It's always been difficult to know what makes Dr. Lewis tick.
那是因为她尴尬 拘束 害羞
That's because she's awkward, and formal and shy.
她挚爱的人已经死了
The love of her life is dead.
劳伦失去纳尼达后 一直在查找
Lauren lost Nadia, then had to keep working
杀害她的真凶
for the people who killed her.
无论如何 她是我仅有的人类盟友
Anyway, she's the only other human ally I've got.
虽然这几天很少见到她
Even though I'm barely human these days.
我们的人在找她
We have people looking for her.
这我听说过 爷爷
Yeah. I've heard that one before, Gramps.
魔术师 诡计
Trickster. Trick.
阁下
Sir.
谢啦 这个...
Thank you. For this...
总之小心一点
Just be careful out there!
邪恶之面千变万化
Evil comes in many faces.
我看到了好多古驰和普拉达
I'm seeing lots of Gucci and Prada...
嗯哼...还有磨皮术 肉毒杆菌
Uh huh... dermabrasions, botox.
- 哈喽 - 简宁特
- Hello! - Janet!
简宁特 医生在吗 我们要见他
Janet, is the Doc in? We need to see him.
在床上有这笑容该多好
Now, with a smile like that, you could talk me
可惜不该在这里
into your bed, but not through those doors.
在我叫警察之前赶紧走
Now, skedaddle before I call the cops.
真正的警察
The real cops.
- 或者... - 或者...
- Or... - Or...
嗷嗷嗷嗷 够了
Ow, ow, ow, ow, okay!
- 坐下 待着 - 要翻滚吗
- Sit. Stay. - Roll over?
- 偷窥者... - 你没必要解雇保姆
- Jeepers Peepers... - You don't have to fire the Nanny.
什么事都没发生
The affair never happened.
你丈夫是在帮奥尔加舒展身体
Your husband was only helping Olga stretch.
让妻子忘掉丈夫的不忠吗
Helping wives forget their husbands cheated on them?
真高尚的催眠
What a noble calling.
尖吻鲈 医生 我们想问你一些问题
Dr. Snook. We have some questions for you.
你似乎在给人们灌输错误的记忆
Seems you've been messing with the wrong people's memory.
我们先到这里 简宁特
We're done here. Janet,
你能帮我 呃 收钱吗
could you, um, get the, uh, bill?
这边 亲爱的... 来这边
Come on, darling. Okay... this way.
好的 做的很好
Yep, you were great.
往这走... 好的
This way... okay.
哦 看看你...
Oh, look at you...
你真行 伙计
Nice one, buddy.
至于你们的好奇心 - 我还是 呃...
As for you curious carps. - I'm, um...
嘿嘿 冷静点
Hey, hey! Snook, chill.
只是问你几个问题
Just want to ask you a few questions.
不不 抱歉 尖吻鲈 只做记忆抽出
No, no, sorry. Snook only does memory extractions.
不做记忆修复
He does not restore them.
不过 这活干得漂亮啊
Although, that is some beautiful work...
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我们都忘记了吧
I guess we forgot.
噢...
Oh...
不出所料... 转形者也有记忆线圈
as expected ... the shifter does have a Recuerdo coil.
不过正如尖吻鲈 所说的... 不是我干的
But like Snook explained... this is not my work.
好吧好吧 所以你想说
Okay. Okay, so what you're saying is somebody's
有人抽出了我们的记忆
been in here extracting our memories?
- 嗯 - 真令人不安
- Mm-hmm. - This is very disturbing
是的 你在说 也许我超级出名
Yeah, you're telling me. I could be famous.
我可能是卡戴珊吗
I could be a Kardashian?
你可能超害羞
You could be shy.
这人要很有天份
Someone very talented...
而且比尖吻鲈 要强大的多
and someone infinitely more powerful than Snook.
这个级别的记忆咒语
A memory spell of this magnitude,
你得找到并破坏那个记忆罗盘
you'd need to find and shatter the Recuerdo compass.
真邪恶 给我讲讲
Wicked, vault it to me.
易趣网 异种交换?
Ebay? Fae-jiji?
那个罗盘丢在了马达加斯加海滨
The compass was lost off the shore of Madagascar
- 埃斯梅・菲尔斯停留时 - 噢 完了
- when the Esme Fierce ran aground. - Oo, burn.
但据说拥有者花了一大笔钱
But rumor has it, that someone's paid quite a bit of money
捞了回来
to have it salvaged.
太好了 现在在谁手里
Nice save! So who's got it?
依哥拉姆 一个收藏家
Engelram. The Collector.
尤那达人之前的打击任务
Last bash before the Una Mens
一副总是无精打采的依哥拉姆吗
permanently party poops all-over this town Engelram?
- 是的... - 啊呸
- Yes...? - Ugh!
我听说他画廊里全是从古老异种那抢来的东西
I hear he keeps his gallery of antique-y Fae swag
锁的严严实实的
well under lock and key.
干嘛看我 我得监视富人异种的交易买卖
What, I keep tabs on wealthy Fae dealings.
出于科学研究嘛
For my science. Mmm...
以防万一 我跟戴森讲帮我们
But just in case, I will tell Dyson to score us
留两张票去看那个怂人烂秀
two tickets to this loser recluse's shit show.
不乐意小清新的社交哈?
Not a fan of a nice strawberry social?
跟异种? 知道他们以人类为食
With the Fae? Watching them dance and drink,
还看他们载歌载舞 歌酒升平?
knowing that they feed on my kind?
再别说什么光明黑暗派的假设游戏了
That their whole Dark/Light system is completely hypocritical?
本姑娘还是免了吧
No, thank you.
可是你有漂亮裙子穿哦
You get to wear a pretty dress.
我要走了 谢啦
I gotta jet. Thanks for the Oolong.
你忘记什么事了吗?
Um... Aren't you forgetting something?
人人都健忘的
We are all forgetting something.
我的戒指?
My Kingmoor ring?
谢啦 没别的了?
Thank you. Anything else?
我的夏夜女孩收藏!
My Lass of the Summer's Eve collector's item!
你知道这限量一千份吗?
You know they only made a thousand of these?
姑娘混口饭吃
Girl's gotta eat.
这是什么?
What's this?
哇哦 哇哦 你还好吧?
Whoa, whoa, whoa... are you okay?
把这位客户的一切告诉我
Tell me everything you know about your client.
不不不 我不生气 亲爱的
Oh. No, no, no. I'm not angry, darling.
我真心好奇
I'm genuinely intrigued.
当我说"设计一件配得上"
When I say "design me one last costume
"新黑暗异种领袖服装"时
befitting the new Dark Fae leader",
你怎么给我听成了"打扮一个性爱玩偶"
why do you hear: "Dress me like an asexual hobo?"
- 我... - 啊...
- I... I... - A-a-a...
我真心希望你意识到依哥拉姆的派对
I-I-du-du-do hope you realize Engelram's party
是本季最热最潮的活动
is "the" event of the season,
也是我最后野性的机会
and my last chance to get the freak on.
在议会到达 让一切乐趣荡然无存
Before the Council arrive, to put the moratorium on all fun.
乐趣 比如...
Fun like this, for example...
伐克斯!
Vex!
你无权来此 马默杜克
You got no authority here, Marmaduke.
无权? 我看明明就是个有恋母情结
Authority? All I see is a bully taking out
的恶霸在肆意发泄罢了
his Mommy issues on the help.
你可阻止不了我转化 伐克斯
You can't stop me from shifting, Vex.
一但我变身为狼 就紧扼你的喉咙
And once I'm a wolf, I'm going straight for your throat.
是吧 不好意思我也是个死脑筋
Yeah, well, I'm as stubborn as I am well endowed.
而且很偏爱墨西哥式对峙呢
And I do love a good Mexican Standoff.
好了?
Ol?
照片不错
Nice picture, by the way.
是呀 我跟大家一样惊讶
Yeah, I was as stunned as anyone to find out she had
她让我登上黑暗派的王位
named me heir to the Dark throne, so to speak.
临表涕言 不知所言啊
I shed so many tears.
不过我得坚强
But I had to stay strong.
这是死绝绝小姐希望的
It's what Miss Died-on-the-toilet would have wanted.
那你的先者若得知你要给光明派异种
And what would your predecessor say to you
收藏者舞会的入场卷的话
giving your Light Fae enemies...
又该对你如何评价呢?
tickets to the Collector's ball tonight?
你什么时候喜欢舞会了?
Hmmm... Since when have you liked balls?
我们要找回失去的东西
We need to get back something we've lost.
那我凭什么帮你呢?
And why the hell would I help you do that?
若你不帮
Because if you don't:
那我就告诉尤那达人...
I may have to tell the Una Mens that you...
你夸张了年轻伊娃的让位细节
exaggerated the details of young Evony's demise.
什么?!
What?!
我那时闻得到她 伐克斯
I can smell her back there, Vex.
- 她小小的细胞 - 她死了
- In her little cell. - She died.
腐朽不堪 没错 可她还没死绝
Oh, she's rotten, all right, but she's not rotting .
- 没人帮忙结束掉? - 你个疯子
- Not man enough to finish the job? - You're mental.
对伊娃来讲真是憾事啊
It's a shame about Evony, you know?
她是邪恶又神经质 不过是个好对手
She was evil and insane, but she was a worthy foe.
比你这个领袖强十倍
And ten times the leader you'll ever be.
好消息是...
The good news is...
你给三张依哥拉姆晚会的邀请
you cough up 3 invitations to Engelram's little shin dig.
我不揭发你
And I won't rat you out.
你看如何?
What do you say?
辛西娅? 给探长戴森拿几张
Cynthia? Could you provide Detective Dyson
我们富有盛誉的派对入场卷
with our complimentary party tickets?
没错 我的票
Yes! My tickets!
- 看来我不需要他们了 - 谢啦 伐克斯
- Looks like I won't be needing them. - Thanks a bunch, Vex.
当然 一旦我恢复记忆 我不保证
Of course, I can't guarantee that once I get my memory back,
我会让你保住这饭碗
I'll let you keep this cushy little job.
抑或是你的小命
Or your life.
别冲我笑 你个贱人
Stop smiling at me, you smug bitch.
这曾经是精神之夜
This used to be a spirit night.
我曾是阿什 如今却是耻辱
I used to be the Ash and now I'm a disgrace.
别让我在大庭广众下 泣不成声
Don't see me crying... in public.
姑娘们都在摇摆...
Lot of ladies shaking their, uh... baby grands.
- 我可不在乎... - 好吧
- Not that I mind... - Yeah, well...
每年 一位女孩被选中单独会见收藏者
every year, one girl gets chosen to meet the elusive collector.
私会 富得流油吧
Elusive, as in, filthy rich.
与钱无关 也不是无价的异种收藏
It's not the money, or his collection of priceless Fae memorabilia.
依哥拉姆的双头蛇
Engelram's amphisbaena.
- 实现愿望的? - 没错
- A wish granter? - Yep.
有些幸运女生美梦成真了
So some lucky lady gets her deepest desires granted.
那不错啊
That's nice.
希望我的女神来了
I wish my lady would get here.
趾裂?
Toe cleavage?
真裂? 浓郁假发?
Real cleavage? Mata Hari wig?
嗨
Holla!
是肯吉
It's Kenzi.
我明白我们关系没那么好
Uh... I know we weren't always... copacetic.
可我现在急需你的灵光假设
But I could use your nerdy hypothesis on some color blocking right now.
我只愿你一切平安
And, um... I just hope... you're safe.
那么...
So...
如果收到这条信息 打给我 回个电话 劳伦
you know, if you get this, call me, call me back... Lauren.
好的 再见
Okay, bye.
你最好是来这推销饰品的
You better be here to advise on accessories.
我的新玩具 你想近看吗?
My new toy. You want a closer look?
瞧我烦什么傻?
Oh, what am I saying?
你这种女孩当然想近看看了
Girls like you always want a closer look.
什么耽搁了? 我一小时前就打给你了
What took you so long? I called you, like, an hour ago.
这东西可要鞭打的 转念一想 我也需要
This stuff doesn't whip itself. Come to think of it, neither do I.
东西给我
Give it to me.
火花提取哦
Wooo... Spark extract,
我家货可是来自与灵魂深处哦
mined straight from the genitals of a sprite.
别过度推销了
Ya, don't oversell it.
你还是让专业的来吧
You better let a professional handle this.
就这样?
That's it?
你的上两次都是记账来的
You're already on the books for your last two visits.
- 知道了 - 当然 如果现金周转不灵
- Noted. - Of course if cash flow is a problem,
还有别的方式能付嘛
there are always other ways to pay.
你没把我变成异种 你玩我
You didn't make me Fae. You tricked me.
我是只人类待宰羔羊躲在精灵的衣服下罢了
Now, I'm just a hot human sheep in twinkly fairy clothing.
那么躲在我天才捏造的伪装下
So shed my brilliantly concocted disguise
看看议会来敲你家门时
and see what happens when when the Council
会发生什么事吧
comes knocking on your door.
马西莫 拜托
Massimo, please.
我会给你钱的
I'll get your money.
很好 要不下次
Good. Or next time,
我会带咬人的东西来哦
I'll show up with something with teeth.
我应该去审审那位 你觉得如何?
Maybe I should interrogate that one? What do you say?
还真是对你的口味
You certainly got a type.
- 肯吉 - 肯吉?
- Kenzi. - Kenzi?
天啊
Oh, my God...
嗨 你们觉得怎么样?
Hi... Hi. What do you think?
我觉得你迟到了
I think you're late.
依哥拉姆已经选了他最喜欢的
And Engelram already has his eye on a favorite.
我还是能吸引他注意力 拿到罗盘针的
I can still get the compass. Get his attention.
你成功吸引我的注意啦
You've got my attention.
听着 你可不能带只狼
Look, I'm just saying you don't bring a wolf
来照看羊
to guard the sheep.
- 什么意思? - 看见那俩个了?
- What does that mean? - You see those two?
他们可是体育画册的封面
They've been on the cover of Sports Illustrated.
我喜欢运动
I like sports.
也许除了你的众多才能外
I'm just saying that despite your many talents,
这是你从未涉及的领域
maybe this is a little outside of your area of expertise.
我是说 我们需要个甜心杀手
I mean, we need a killer kiss here.
我会让你知道
I will have you know
我可勾引过不少款爷
that I have seduced many a rich-dork before.
大概吧
I think.
你到底还想不想要我们的记忆了?
Okay, do you want to get our memories back or not?
并忘了这个诡异瞬间?
And forget this magic moment?
你想看看我的技术活哈?
You wanna see my 'skill set'?
没问题 但愿你的筋骨活动开了
Fine. I hope you stretched.
嗨 你能帮我买杯酒吗?
Hi! Can you buy me a free drink?
- 似曾相识 - 不 我是柯丽鸥
- Deja vu. - No, I'm Clio.
似曾相识什么的都是虚话
Deja vu came down with a case of the crabs.
聪明
Charming.
天啊
Oh, my God...
我认识你
I know you.
你是个警察
Wow... you're a cop.
不管这是什么花招? 我不感兴趣
Whatever this is? I'm not interested.
- 我是仙女精 - 我真心不感兴趣
- I am a nymph. - Now I'm really not interested.
- 真伤人 - 被伤过 好吗?
- Ouch. - Just bad memories, you know?
醉倒龙舌兰 全裸
Tequila-soaked, nakedness.
我们可不都那么坏
You know, we're not all bad.
我们那样产卵罢了
We're just kind of spawned that way.
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four...
- 一 二 三 四 - 别数了 黑尔
- One, two, three, four... - Stop counting, Hale.
把我抱紧点 我可不是你的诺娜
And hold me closer, I'm not your Nona.
别扭了
Stop squirming.
该死 你现在就好像要扒我的衣服!
Dammit, act like you wanna tear my clothes off!
神啊
Oh, golly.
这比你想要搭话还来得尴尬
That's more awkward than your attempt at small talk.
我同意 对不起
I agree. Excuse me.
- 伙计 她是我舞伴 - 当然不是
- I got it, partner. - You really don't.
那个深色皮肤女人是谁?
Who's the brunette?
你能闭会嘴 让我领着你么?
Would you just shut up and let me lead for once?
认真的?
Seriously?
也许我们原来做过这件事
Maybe we have done this before.
那个 我会记住的
That, I would remember.
最后一次托举
The final rose.
太原创了
How original.
看起来好像有些人要去私人住所了
Looks like someone's going private chambers.
当然 去掠夺战利品
Pirate booty, sure.
为什么不呢
Stuffed unicorn... Why not.
有人吗?
Hello?
极好的关门!
Great door!
太大声了
Really loud.
我喜欢这些箱子 十足的
And I love all your crates. Very Pottery Barn.
这个场景是不是像
Is this situation going Indecent Proposal?
因为我需要看看提前看看宝石 伙计
'Cause I'm gonna need to see the jewels up front, buddy.
欢迎...可爱的女孩
Welcome... pretty girl.
依哥拉姆先生?
Mr. Engelram?
很高兴为您服务务务
At your sssservice.
请别因为我而停下!
Please, don't stop yourselves on my account!
该结婚就结婚吧!
Make merry while ye may!
因为尤那达人正在来的路上!
For The Una Mens are on their way!
我也在我的路上!
And I'll be on mine, too!
当你勉强说出
As soon as you cough up what I,
黑暗派庄严的长老 也就是我 想要的
the venerable leader of the Dark, want.
那就是我想要的东西:狼
And what I want: is the Wolf.
嗷嗷嗷嗷
Ooowwww!
给我点钱 我带你离开这里
I can get you out of here for a price.
我认为我更想扯断他的喉咙
I think I'd rather stay; rip out his throat.
你知道怎么用绳子下去吗?
Do you know how to rappel?
怎么 你从伊诗比蒂裙子上拿到了绳子?
Why, you got some rope in that itty bitty dress?
我需要做什么吗?...凭自己?
Do I have to do everything... myself?
哦 尖吻鲈
Oh, Snook.
哦 你自力更生吧 老狼
Oh, you're on your own, Wolf.
你是什么?
What are you?
一个你的忠实舞迷...
a big fan of your dancing...
我是阿佩斯纳蜥蜴龙
And I am Amphisbaena.
慢点滚 斯莱特林
Slow your roll, Slytherin.
我只是想向里看看
I merely want to look inside.
所以我可以同意你未出口的愿望
So I may grant your unspoken wish.
不用了 我会说出来
No need, I'll speak it.
我想要里卡德・蒙特尔班
I want the Ricardo Montalban...
里克・马丁
Ricky Martin...
呃
Uh, the, the Compass thing-y.
就这些?
That's it?
好吧...我还想要你的独角兽
Well... I'll take your unicorn too,
如果你想裁员的话
if you're looking to downsize.
看起来你的欲望永无止境啊
Just when it comes to unlimited wishes,
你这个肤浅的女人
you kind of landed on sssshallow.
好吧 你说话的样子
Well, you're one to talk.
就像那些学步小孩
Like those toddler-esque pores happen au natural.
现在
Now, now.
我只是每两个月蜕一次皮
I simply shed my skin every two months.
- 太不公平了 - 你可以试试
- That is so unfair. - You could try...
在你昏倒之前卸一下妆
removing your makeup before you pass out
在午夜之时享用奶酪玉米和伏特加
atop your midnight helping of cheese popcorn and vodka.
我 啊哦
Me-ow.
- 回到话题上来? -对 不好意思
- Back to the task at hand? - Right. Sorry.
我只是认为渺小的人类会有欲望
I merely thought the little human would wish
想要回报
for her return.
不
No.
还有 什么?
Also, what?
很遗憾
Pity.
你不知道你失去了什么么么
You don't know what you're misssssing.
我知道我想离开了
I know I'd like to get out of here
在你整个吞下我之前 所以
before you swallow me whole, so...
谢啦
thank you.
- 你叫我人类 - 我早就该发现了
- You called me human. - I should have realized it ssssooner.
你的探戈跳的太无力了
There was something so vulnerable about your tango...
- 噢 眼镜蛇大人 - 我给过你机会
- Oh, Cobra Commander. - I granted your wish,
现在我要整吞了你
now I "am" going to swallow you whole.
这不是很公平嘛
Isn't that a fair trade?
装扮不错呀 伐克斯
Nice costume, Vex.
你去年不还是个小挫样吗
Weren't you the impotent dick last year?
哼 现在是时候来看看是谁厉害
Well, now it's time to see who really is the bitch.
而谁刚刚死了
And who's just dead.
你大老远到这来
Did you come all the way down here just
就为了向我展示新鞋子吗
to show me your pretty new shoes?
恐怕不是 这是为了铭记
Hardly. This is about remembering.
或者 是确保没人记得
Or, making sure that no one else does.
你也失忆了
Your memory's gone, too.
我早就知道啦
I worked it out ages ago.
- 这才能解释一切 - 真的吗
- It's the only thing that makes sense. - really.
这更不对劲了
This is making less and less sense.
你真的认为我该成为莫瑞根吗
Do you really think I was meant to be the Morrigan?
我以前从未有过权力 我是说 不像这样
I've never really had power before. I mean, not like this.
如果
And what if...
大家的记忆会导致他们
the thing everyone remembers leads them
挑战我努力争取来的统治
to challenge my hard-fought reign?
我会不择手段来重掌权利
I did terrible things to get my mesmer back.
我都觉得很可怕
Even for me.
为我泪流成河吧伐克斯
Cry me a river, Vex.
我仍然会做噩梦 梦到自己孤独无助
I still have nightmares about being helpless.
无足轻重 穷困潦倒
Unable to influence. Unable to feed.
但是 这...嗯
But, this... hm...
这样对我来说是最好的结果
this is about as good as it gets for me.
如果我让肯吉和大家想起没有我一切都很好
And I'm damned if I'm gonna let Kenzi let everyone else
那我就完蛋了
recall how good it was to be without me!
那现在要怎么办呢 伐克斯
How's this going to work, Vex?
你不能再催眠我一次了 我转变了
You can't mesmer me once.I shift.
对 不过... 还好我可以催眠你的同伴
Yeah, well... it's a good thing I can mesmer your mate!
伐克斯 别动他
Vex! Leave him out of this!
苍天啊
Evan-nescence!!
你什么时候这么大题小做了
Since when do you do the dramatic?
你想玩点大的吗
You want drama?
那我就杀了你
I'm gonna end you.
小箱子...
Small crate...
大箱子 蛇精来啦
big crate, snake man coming...
加油 小肯
Come on, Kenzi...
加油 你没朋友 没天赋 快长树枝呀
come on, you no friends, no talent, Glow Stick... !
好吧
Okay...
还我 不不不
"Pay me." No, no, no.
我要重新变回人类
Of all times to get my human back on... !
你曾经和我们并肩作战
You fought by our side!
对不起
Guilty!
你违反了伊娃协议
You betrayed our agreement about Evony!
再来呀
Harder!!!
你是爱肯吉的 你怎么能这么对她
You love Kenzi! How could you do this to her?!
我们都爱肯吉
We all love Kenzi.
可是你的手下正在处理她呢
Hell, your Alpha Male's 'doing' her right now...
前艾什真要杀了莫瑞根吗
Is the former Ash really gonna kill the current Morrigan?
我觉得尤那达人不会同意的
I don't think the Una Mens would like that.
那只有一个办法来证实了
There's only one way to find out.
- 大狼爪 - 忘了告诉你 发型真不错哦
- Massive Wolf Paws... - Forgot to tell you: love the hair.
哦 我的...
Oh, my...
伊娃
Aife?
好久不见了
It's been a long time...
你好 爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
指南针
The Compass!
- 它坏了 - 是因为被那个破坏了吗
- It cracked... - Well, did that do it?
不 你还有菜籽油
No, you still got canola oil.
等下...也许我们要让指针和北极重合
Wait... maybe we have to align the needle to the true North.
明白
Roger that.
- 肯吉... - 怎么了
- Kenzi... - What??
- 你一直都在我身边 - 你也是
- You've always been there for me. - And you for moi.
我愿为你献出生命
I would give my life for you.
永不抛弃你
I'd never desert you.
也许伐克斯是对的 这是最好的结果
Maybe Vex is right. Maybe this is as good as it gets.
也许
Maybe...
也许我们可以再进一步
Maybe we can make it better.
我..大概有八十条丁字裤
I... have, like, eighty thongs.
嗯 很棒啊
Well, that's great.
我是说 我 很孤独
I mean... I am... lonely.
而这 这一切 都是不对的
And this for... all of it, it isn't right.
这段时候都不对
It hasn't been for a while.
而我的 我的心很难受
And my... And my heart hurts.
戴森 我说不出原因
Dyson, and I don't know why.
而且 当你陷入爱里 你会知道的
Besides: when you're in love, you know.
对吧
Right?
嗯
Yeah.
不管发生什么 你和我 一起面对 对吧
Whatever happens, though, you and me, we're in it together, right?
嗯 生死之交 绝不重色轻友
Yes. Friends 'til the end. Bros before hoes.
- 豆吧的好兄弟 - 恩 全部同意
- Pals at the Dal... - Yeah, all that.
嗯
Yeah.
把它给我
Gimme that.
- 波 - 波
- Bo... - Bo...
不
No.
你好呀 爸爸
Hi... Daddy.
伊娃
Aife...
伊娃...别这样
Aife... please...
这是我仅剩的一切了
It's all that I have left.
是我的仇恨支撑我活下来
It's all that's kept me alive! Is my hate!
我知道有一天我们会重聚的
Knowing one day we would have our reunion.
而你会血流成河
And it would end in you spilling your cursed blood.
我会为我们找到她的
I'll find her for us.
这就是为她所做的
This is for "her!"
- 黑尔 黑尔 你没事吧 - 哦他没事
- Hale! Hale, are you okay? - Oh, he's fine.
真不错 海妖音超棒的
Very effective. Splendid siren-ing.
真高兴你没被蛇咬到 小肯
You know, I'm glad you didn't get bitten by the snake, Kenz.
我还得说 真喜欢
And I gotta tell you, I love what you're doing
你最近的睫毛
with your mascara these days.
- 我也是 - 对不起
- I do, too. - I'm so sorry...
不 停 停 我们要找到她
No, stop... stop, we're going to find her.
- 她失踪多久了 - 我们从哪开始
- How long has she even been missing? - Where do we even start?
通过找到
By finding whomever could have erased
消除我们爱的人记忆的家伙
the memory of the one we love most.
哦 你会后悔的 那躺着几个古老的魔术师
Oh, you'll regret it. There lies some old, wild magiks.
不不不 戴森 你不能走
No, no, no... No, Dyson, you can't go now!
最后见到波生还的是塔姆辛
The last person to see Bo alive was Tamsin.
好吧 那你还等什么 快去
Well, then what are you waiting for?! Go, go!!!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
小肯 我们要谈谈
Kenz... we need to talk.
她没回来之前 我都没法呼吸
Not until she's back. I can't even... breathe.
我得走了 好么 我得走了
I gotta go. Okay, I gotta go...
波
Bo?
Bo...
噢 我想起来了...
Oh... I remember...